YASH KINARIWALA

Atlanta, GA

Yashkinariwalask95@gmail.com l 678 – 697 – 8718

Portfolio | LinkedIn | GitHub

SUMMARY

Versatile Full Stack Developer with 2+ years of experience designing, developing, and managing complex sites and internal frameworks. Specializes in ReactJS and responsive design. Passionate about approaching programming challenges from different angles and collaborating with others to create meaningful web applications.

SKILLS

- Expert in HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, ReactJS, NodeJS, WordPress
- Knowledge of SQL, MongoDB, ExpressJS, Bootstrap, Handlebars, Firebase, C, C++, .NET [C#], Git
- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator)

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer Atlanta, GA

Full Stack Web Developer / Designer

August 2017 – Present

- Working as designer and developer to develop a custom HTML/CSS, JavaScript, MySQL and CMS based website and optimized assets for web such as Logo, Business card, Brochures with Adobe Creative Suite.
- Developing and designing various user-friendly websites for clients using the latest and optimized web
- Developed complex graphics and professional designs for a variety of businesses, organizations, professionals and individuals, including custom graphic and logo design.
- Used CMS system a WordPress developed several websites for clients which could lead to increase in annual business profitability by 40%. See here MobileCareUSA, VioletHairSalon, SutraLounge

RV DESIGN Atlanta, GA

Exterior Designer

JUNE 2017 – JANUARY 2018

- Rendered multiple exterior elevation by using tools such as Adobe photoshop and illustrator.
- Rendered Front Elevation uses the architect's drawings.
- Developed graphic images and effects to achieve design goals.

AIM CONSULTANT LTD

Ahmedabad, India

Investment Advisor

JUNE 2016 - MAY 2017

- Provided investment advisory services for existing clients to support their current trading activities on the financial markets of India to help preserve and grow wealth.
- Created multiple algorithms to find best stock trade as per current market position.
- Managed an investment portfolio of 32 lakh rupees for existing clients.
- Experienced with buying and selling stocks in four (4) different types: Future, Future Plus, Option and Cash.

EDUCATION

Georgia Institute of Technology

Full Stack Web Development Program

MAY 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018

L.J INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY

Atlanta, GA

Atlanta, GA

JUNE 2013 - MAY 2016

Bachelor's In Computer Application